

# BESAYTE, JOMAR KRISTOFFER L.

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

- Blk 1 Lot 10 Phase 7, ACM Woodstock Homes Alapan 1-A Imus, Cavite
- code.besaytejomarkristoffer@gmail.com
- 0995 155 4235

# **ABOUT ME**

Experienced Web Developer with a history in freelance as a Fullstack Web Developer. Skilled in Web Development, Database Management, and Quality Assurance Testing. Graduated in July 2024 with Latin Honors in Bachelor of Science in Information Technology from Bicol University. With my given skills and experience, I am open for any job position for employment.

## **LINKS**

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jomarkristoffer-besayte-587256312/

#### GitHub:

https://github.com/twopiiii

#### REFERENCE

- Mgr. Daniel P. Esguerra
  DBP Provident Fund Department Senior Manager
- AM Cielo S. Gregorio
  DBP Provident Fund Department
  Assistant Manager

## **LANGUAGE**

- English
- Filipino

## **SKILLS**

- Web Development
- Quality Assurance Testing
- Database Management
- Microsoft Office
- Critical Thinking and Problem Solving
- Adaptability

#### **EDUCATION**

#### BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

**Bicol University** | College Level (2020 -2024)

Legazpi City, Albay, Philippines

- Graduated with Latin Honors (Cum Laude)
- · Consistent Dean's Lister

#### SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGY, ENGINEERING, AND MATHEMATICS +

**University of Santo Tomas - Legazpi** | Senior High Level (2018 -2020) Legazpi City, Albay, Philippines

Graduated with Honors

## **EXPERIENCE**

CivilTech-Connect: Cultivating Career Paths and Navigation for Future and
 Current Civil Technologists (Sept. 2024 - Dec. 2024)

Fullstack Web Developer | Quality Assurance Tester

- Developed a website for Civil Technologists, offering tailored educational resources, networking opportunities, and job support to enhance their professional development and success.
- Developed an admin page that operates CRUD.
- Reviewed and analyzed product specifications
- Continuously reported and collaborated with stakeholders
- Identified bugs, and developed strategies and test plans
- Executed manual test cases based on defined test plans

# Development Bank of the Philippines, Provident Fund Department (Feb. 2024 - May 2024)

Fullstack Web Developer | Quality Assurance Tester

- Developed a website for DBP Provident Fund members that allows them to view all their loan balances, surpluses, contributions, and generate their own Statement of Account (SOA) in their account.
- Developed an admin page that includes CMS, operates CRUD, Generate Statement of Accounts (SOA), and Generate Surplus Statement.
- Reviewed and analyzed product specifications
- Continuously reported and collaborated with stakeholders
- · Identified bugs, and developed strategies and test plans
- Executed manual test cases based on defined test plans

# PAWsitive: A Web-Based Pet Care Veterinary Clinic Management System (Sept. 2023 - Dec. 2023)

Project Manager | Front-end Developer | Quality Assurance Tester

- A startup company that develops a system for Veterinary Clinics.
- The system includes user page, admin page, staff page, and an automated SMS used for appointment confirmations and reminders.
- Reviewed and analyzed product specifications
- Continuously reported and collaborated with stakeholders
- Identified bugs, and developed strategies and test plans
- · Executed manual test cases based on defined test plans